In our own history, there's nothing that expresses a massive civil disobedience any more than the Boston Tea Party,
and yet we give this to our young people and our students as a part of the great tradition of our nation.
So I think we're in good company when we break unjust laws,
and I think those who are willing to do it and accept the penalty are those who are part of the saving of the nation.
When we look back on these times, they will say that this is the week the revolution began.
We are in a time.
By the way, when I say a time, like y'all be hearing me say like, it was a time, it was a time.
What I mean in Amanda speak is I'm referring to an era of a certain set of memories, of values, of experiences that can be shared amongst the people.
Like 2005, the crunk era, it was a time.
I come in a club, I'm sick of my dress.
Okay, back to what I was saying.
Like we're in a time, and I don't know that a lot of people are grasping that, but we are actually living history right now.
And I say that I don't know if a lot of people are grasping that because so many people seem to really take this day-to-day thing too far in the fact that they don't grasp that there are befores, there are nows, and there are afters.
They don't seem to see the continuance of the journey, and so they don't seem to understand that what you're doing now can affect where the journey goes.
What you're doing now may seem like a very small grain of sand in the bigger picture, but if everyone's grain of sands are dropped in the same space, then now you've made a hill to impact, and that hill can stop whatever's coming.
So you have to think of everything you're doing as mattering, and it's important not because it's trying to say that you are being egotistical or arrogant, but it really expounds upon the reality that we are all here together, and we are all here in community, and the people who are causing problems for everyone don't have that mindset.
The people who cause problems believe that they can change, and that they don't need nobody else to do it.
The people who cause the issues, they have an arrogance that is actually confidence, because arrogance is really just fake security.
Confidence is real security. They're just using theirs for bad.
We need to be employing that same energy for good. We need to be believing in ourselves.
We need to be knowing that even the smallest thing that we do towards good is still moving towards good, and when we hold ourselves to that standard of obligation, we move different.
But if you don't think that what's mattering now or what's happening now is really going to matter in two weeks or two years, then you're not going to maybe think that way, but I need us to think that way.
And I'm telling you, I believe that this is the week that they will say the revolution began, and when it happens later on, and you're talking about this time, you will want to be able to say, this is what I contributed, even if it is just a small portion.